http://www.calagcu.org/about-us/privacy-policy

We will be closed on Thursday, December 24 and Friday, December 25 for the Christmas holiday.
SKIP TO CONTENT
Contact Us
Search
Online Banking Login
HomeJoin UsHow to JoinEligible GroupsAccounts & ServicesChecking AccountsShare Savings AccountsDirect DepositMoney TransfersMember BenefitsLoansVehicle LoansVISA Credit CardPersonal LoansYamaha ProductsAccount AccesseStatementsMobile Banking24-Hour Telephone AccessBranch LocationATM AccessText Me an ATMCU Service CentersRatesLoan RatesSavings RatesReal Estate RatesFee ScheduleResourcesHome Loan CenterCalAgCU VISA Card RewardsShared Branches and ATMsHelpful Web ResourcesAbout UsContact UsHoliday ScheduleBoard of Directors & StaffHistoryWho We ServeEmploymentPrivacy PolicyDisclosuresAccessibility
Menu
Online Banking Login
Disclosures: Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.
Thank you for visiting the California Agribusiness Credit Union site. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this CalAgCU site.
The Information We CollectAt some CalAgCU sites, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).
How We Use the InformationWe may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to confirm your reservation of a CalAgCU meeting, when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your membership with us.
We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.
The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.
Agents and contractors of CalAgCU who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for CalAgCU.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.
If a CalAgCU site discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by or affiliated with CalAgCU who want to market products or services to you, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses.
CalAgCU may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, click here for instructions on how to make your request.
Finally, CalAgCU sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and SponsorsSome of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
CalAgCU sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. CalAgCU has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. The CalAgCU site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.
CookiesTo enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.
Our Commitment to SecurityWe have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.
How You Can Access or Correct InformationFor instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this CalAgCU site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email us.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns about the CalAgCU online policy for this site or its implementation you may email us.
Find an ATM
ZIP CODE
Text a Zip Code to 91989to find nearby ATM Locations
Find out more
Find a branch
ZIP CODE
Text a Zip Code to 91989to find nearby branch Locations
Become a member
Join today
HomeJoin UsHow to JoinEligible GroupsAccounts & ServicesChecking AccountsShare Savings AccountsDirect DepositMoney TransfersMember BenefitsLoansVehicle LoansVISA Credit CardPersonal LoansYamaha ProductsAccount AccesseStatementsMobile Banking24-Hour Telephone AccessBranch LocationATM AccessText Me an ATMCU Service CentersRatesLoan RatesSavings RatesReal Estate RatesFee ScheduleResourcesHome Loan CenterCalAgCU VISA Card RewardsShared Branches and ATMsHelpful Web ResourcesAbout UsContact UsHoliday ScheduleBoard of Directors & StaffHistoryWho We ServeEmploymentPrivacy PolicyDisclosuresAccessibility
